Contact

9084634387 (Home) me@jeremycimafonte.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jbcima (LinkedIn) www.of.agency (Company)

Top Skills

User Experience Software Design Mobile Web Design

Certifications
Design Sprint

Jeremy Cimafonte

Founder, Creative Director at Agency of San Francisco, California

Summary

Working with startups and big brands has given me the opportunity to learn.

Then, founded Agency of inc. to collaborate with a creative team under the belief that a group of interdisciplinary experts combining their potential can quickly solve business problems, and craft valuable experiences across brand and product.

Want concentrated expertise integrated as your internal team? Learn more at: https://www.of.agency

Experience

Agency of
Founder, Creative Director
May 2018 - Present (2 years 1 month)
Greater New York City Area

An agency of experts creating cohesive experiences across brand and product.

http://www.of.agency

- Creating a culture that embraces diverse perspectives, remote collaboration, and creative opportunity to drive business value for clients.
- Lead the development and execution of the vision, mission, and overall strategy and process.
- Leadership and creative direction

Artificial Intelligence Startup Lead Designer September 2017 - April 2018 (8 months) San Francisco Bay Area

Consumer Artificial Intelligence projects.

Lead design for a consumer recommendations platform, powered by AI.

Page 1 of 3

- Conducted weekly user research to inform product strategy & design
- Developed and implemented a product strategy and roadmap with the team.
- Created wireframes, design, and worked with engineers to ship features.
- · Worked with a team of other creatives, and freelancers.

Freelance, self-employed Freelance Designer 2016 - 2017 (1 year) Greater New York City Area

Worked on multiple freelance projects.

- Product design and some development for small startups
- Various design work for advertising agencies.

Jawbone

KPCB Design Fellow May 2014 - September 2014 (5 months) san francisco, california

At Jawbone I worked on the growth portion of the design team. We were tasked with using design to explore areas of growth and ship solutions.

- Responsible for the redesign of the Jawbone UP App Store (with the goal of increasing partner integration).
- Early concepts, prototypes, and coding for the UP smartwatch app leading the charge to open the platform for other devices.
- Designs and prototypes for numerous other UP features (such as UP and American Express integration).

Brewster

Designer and Engineer August 2013 - May 2014 (10 months) Noho

I was the principal designer on a small engineering team. I lead design (web and mobile) part time from mockup to shipped release.

- Drove redesign of on-boarding flow to grow user base and simplify user experience.
- Led design of pivot from address book to syncing service.

Trendalytics
hackNY Fellow
June 2013 - August 2013 (3 months)

NYC

Guided user experience efforts through working with the team.

- Designed and developed front end interface for fashion monitoring and analytics platform.
- · conducted initial user research and feedback
- worked with team to collaborate on paper mockups
- implemented using AngularJS, D3, HighCharts and performed user testing

Complex Media
Marketing Web Developer
July 2012 - May 2013 (11 months)
Manhattan, NYC

- Conceptualized and executed responsive web app for nationwide 'McDonald's FlavorBattle' campaign.
- Conceptualized and executed responsive web app for nationwide "Miller Lite Stand Up Comedy Tour."
- Designed and developed custom and engaging ad units for Nike, Axe, and other brands
- Developed online marketing campaigns (including microsites, ad units, etc.) for Sony Pictures, FX Networks, and other brands
- developed front end ad generator for creating and automating marketing campaigns
- · developed optimized modular ad targeting and serving script

Education

Tufts University
Bachelor's Degree · (2011 - 2016)